
Namecheap Advanced DNS click-by-click guide for tradehax.net

1) Log in to Namecheap and open Domain List.
2) Click Manage next to tradehax.net.
3) Open the Advanced DNS tab.
4) Delete existing records for host @ and www.
5) Add this record:
   Type: A
   Host: @
   Value: 76.76.21.21
   TTL: Automatic
6) Add this record:
   Type: CNAME
   Host: www
   Value: cname.vercel-dns.com
   TTL: Automatic
7) Save all changes and wait 5-30 minutes for propagation.
8) Verify from terminal:
   namecheap-dns-copypasta.bat verify

